I will have to offer
my gratitude to Lord Ains,
for allowing this many
of our membership to gather for this.
I, Demiurge, have been granted
all authority for this,
by the word of Lord Ains.
Sebas, do you object?
Of course not.
Then I hope you are not
under any mistaken impressions.
The reason why
our membership has assembled
is to execute Eight Fingers,
who were foolish enough
to spit in the honored faces
of the Supreme Ones.
I understand that. Rescuing Tuare
is a secondary objective.
That is correct. I share your hope
that Tuare be rescued alive,
because I do not believe that
she can withstand resurrection magic.
So then, Demiurge, do we have
any information on Eight Fingers?
Oh, I don't think that will be a problem.
We've already obtained information
on locations for seven of their bases.
Also, Sebas, allow me to apologize upfront,
but I cannot reveal the full scope
of the plans I am about to lay out to you.
Since you will return to Nazarick
immediately after Tuare is recovered,
you will no longer be concerned with them.
I understand.
Solution, I ask that you back Sebas up.
Very well, Lord Demiurge.
Next, I must convey
an important matter to you.
Entoma?
Acknowledged.
You are forbidden to kill this person.
Especially you, Shalltear.
Okay, I get it!
You don't have to single me out!
Hmm? What is it, Shadow Demon?
I see. It appears we now have
one more Eight Fingers base to attack.
Mare, I want you to head there with Entoma.
Right. Um, please, leave them to us.
We must show Lord Ains that we are
of service to him through this mission.
Failure is not an option. On the contrary,
see that you provide results that will
wipe the slate clean of any mistakes.
Wh-What about me?
Shalltear, I hate to do this to you,
but you stand down.
Ah, I am concerned
about your Blood Frenzy.
O-Okay, fine! That's just fine!
Now, let me detail the second stage
of the plan, "Gehenna."
That's such nice mythril armor, right?
Are you sure you want to dye it like that?
I got it from Princess Renner,
but it just stands out too much.
However, it's virtually silent,
so I think it's suitable for infiltrating.
Captains, gather around!
We're going to go over the plan!
We are about to launch a simultaneous raid
on eight buildings in Eight Fingers' possession,
and take control of them.
But we only have seven squads.
Once we've taken control
of our assigned buildings,
those of us here will head for
the last location that we've identified.
In other words, first come, first served, right?
Our enemy is a force of heavyweights
who control an underground society.
Be plenty cautious.
The squads are all ready.
There are some former
orichalcum class adventurers here, too,
courtesy of Marquis Raeven.
Lockmeyer. Nice to meet you.
Hey, virgin!
Miss Gagaran, is something the matter?
Oh, I was just thinking you might be nervous,
so maybe I'd give you
a pat on your virgin behind.
You must be Brain Unglaus.
Indeed...
--Do I pass?
--Huh?
She's here to check out if I'm a warrior
she can entrust with you, Climb.
Is that true?
Hell no! It doesn't matter to me
what happens to you.
But with you along,
things should go more easily.
Best not to get too careless. There are
any number of monsters in this world.
Ho, so you're the prudent type.
I'm not averse to a man like that.
You're probably not a virgin,
but what do you say?
I think I'll pass. I'd likely
get crushed under the pressure.
Oh, yeah? That's too bad.
Climb, you watch yourself.
R-Right!
She's a nice enough lady.
Everyone in the Blue Rose is nice.
Well, we should get going, too.
Right.
Wait, wait! It's me! I just got back.
Mr. Lockmeyer...
After using invisibility magic
and sneaking in, I learned two things--
There's a woman being held captive
in the building's prison cell.
Also, there are five people here who
fit the description of Six Arms members.
That... is terrible news,
but it's also terrific news, isn't it?
If Six Arms is gathered here,
it means that the other locations
will fall pretty easily.
So what do we do?
It's going to be impossible
for just us to take this place.
We fall back.
You're right. We have no choice--
Is that...?
What a coincidence,
running into you fellows here.
Lord Sebas, what are you
doing here at this hour?
As it happens, the woman that
I mentioned saving has been kidnapped.
I am here because I received a summons.
Then she must be...
Can you tell us more
about the woman in the cell?
Mm-hmm.
I see...
Then five of the Six Arms
are grouped together here?
Lord Sebas, if you are willing,
would you mind working with us?
Of course. I was called to be here, after all.
So then, I will take on the Six Arms members.
Thank you very much.
I will go in through the front.
While I have the enemy's attention,
I would appreciate it if you could rescue Tuare.
Understood!
What should those of us sneaking in do?
With just the three of us,
our magic caster should be able
to cast an invisibility spell on us.
The other squad members
aren't up for sneaking in,
thanks to the sound their armor makes.
I swear, we will bring
Miss Tuare back safely with us.
I would be much obliged.
Right on time. Come in.
We've been expecting you.
We're looking forward to some more today.
Aren't there... supposed to be five of you?
Old man, I hear you're quite strong.
Don't tell me you're the one
who defeated Succulent.
I don't care if he is a has-been,
having one of the Six Arms be defeated
right in front of Cocco Doll,
chief of the slave trade,
is embarrassing beyond words.
Well, he insisted that
he was beaten by Brain Unglaus.
Either way, old man, you're the one
that started all this trouble.
We'll kill you first. Look up there.
There are bigwigs
from all over sitting up there.
They're here to watch us torture you to death.
Is that Zero fellow up there, as well?
Why, yes he is.
What was that? Are you trying to pick a fight?
Please pay it no mind.
Now, where is she? Where is Tuare?
What if I said she was dead?
Would you really be that kind to her?
You're right. We wouldn't be that kind.
The woman is one of the gifts we have
for Cocco Doll. She's safely secure.
Since you're all here,
all of you attack me at once.
Do so, and you will last at least ten seconds.
Listen to you, you human!
I'm sure he must not have ever
met anyone who was truly strong before.
Well, okay. We'll take you on.
Malmvist, of the Thousand Kills.
Edström, of the Dancing Scimitar.
Peshurian, of the Spatial Slash.
And me, Davernoch, the Undead King.
Undead King, you say?
An overblown nickname for a fool such as you!
There is only one person in this world
who can claim the nickname of "Undead King."
The presumptuousness
of an inferior undead like you!
Solution! Did you find Zero?
He does not appear to be here.
That means another ten seconds.
Here it is.
Are you Miss Tuare?
What is going on?!
Say there, little girl...
...or boy...?
What are you doing in here?
L-Lady, are you the most important
person in the mansion?
No--er, yes I am. I'm the
most important person in the mansion.
S-So you are. Thank goodness.
Um, so anyway, uh, we're leaving.
Ah! My leg!
Ow! Ow! Stop! Oh, stop!
We have to hurry and get going.
I'll let you handle things from here.
Okay!
Everybody, keep moving the last
of that stuff quickly, okay?
Mmm... Ah, I haven't eaten it yet!
Oopsie, oopsie!
Nothing beats man flesh when dieting, huh?
Yo! What are you munching down on
that seems so tasty to you?
Some meat.
From a human.
You don't say. I didn't think that
Eight Fingers kept any monsters!
You know what? Can we pretend
like we never saw each other?
Sorry about this, but I'm one of
the top adventurers in the kingdom.
I can't very well say "Oh, okay"
to a man-eating monster and let it go.
This is so much trouble. Still, you're strong.
Maybe I'll turn you into preserved food.
Huh? Is running away all you can do?
Hmm, you sure love
whooshing that thing around.
I'll smash you!
These are the finest clothes,
given to me by the Supreme Being.
Wha--?!
What was that?!
Hard Armor Bug!
You see, I'm an entomancer.
So I summon insects like this...
Blade Bug!
...and then I can use them!
I'll kill you now.
I really didn't intend to kill you,
but I can't have this anymore!
You've changed the way you move!
So now you're taking this seriously?!
Thanks, Tia.
Ninja skills?
So Gagaran, your blood flows red, too?
What are you so surprised about?
I thought by now your blood would flow blue.
Like a power-up.
I haven't changed races.
Then, a class change.
Are you just about ready yet?
Spider Talisman!
Shadow Clone Technique!
Hard Bullet Bugs!
Immovable Adamantine Shield Technique!
What is this?!
She defended without even looking at me!
She has a wide field of view?
It's not just that; it's something else.
This is bad. I don't have
the slightest notion that we can win.
I don't need these bugs anymore.
In their place, come here...
Oops. I thought I'd filled up earlier, too.
Must be all the exercise I'm getting,
but I'm getting hungry again.
Flame Burst!
Thunderbird Talisman!
Damn it, I hate things that slither!
Tia!
Thunderbird Swarm Talismans!
Explosive Talisman!
Sharp Cutting Talisman!
Piercing Wind Talisman!
Tia!
You insect punk!
This wasn't the order I was going to eat you in,
but she looks pretty filling,
as well as tasty, so I guess it's fine.
Why don't you stop right there?
Who are you?
Is a man-eating monster wearing
a maid uniform supposed to be a joke?
I can't imagine anyone would be delighted
to have a monster like you attending to them,
with the stench of blood hanging over you.
What did you just say?
Evileye...
I was wondering what
you were up to, but good grief.
Give some thought to
the difference in your abilities!
This one is stronger than you two.
She's also weaker than I am.
How dare you push
my friends around, you monster!
No one would be delighted
to have me attend to them, you say?
You can be smashed
right alongside your friends!
Hmph, what a ridiculous attack.
Reverse Gravity!
Gagaran, you're in the way!
Go heal Tia's wounds, or something!
Are you with that Demon God...?! In that case...
Vermin Bane!
What kind of magic is that?
Insecticide magic-- "Vermin Bane."
It's my own original magic spell.
Her face is dissolving.
Are you telling me that was a bug mask?
A Lip Bug? It devours the vocal cords
of its human victims,
allowing it to produce their voice.
How dare you... How dare you!
Your voice is a lot more
endearing like this, isn't it?
I rather like your voice this way.
You humans!!
Tch! Vermin Bane!
You're the only one...
You're the only one I have to fear...
If I can just kill you, everything else
will go down like a simple job.
Immobilizing Paralysis Technique!
Crystal Lance!
Vermin Bane!
This is unlike earlier. Crystal Wall!
Did you hear that just now?
How can her maid uniform and
my armor have the same hardness?
It's not possible!
Your attack that stings me is getting tedious!
What do we do?
Attack her all at once with some
heavy firepower to wear her down.
That's an answer easy enough
for me to understand.
Okay, let's take it to her.
Acid Splash!
Explosive Talisman!
Immovable Adamantine Shield Technique!
Vermin Bane!
We've beaten her.
I'll finish her off.
Right.
Can I ask you to stop there?
Hey, is that one of Evileye's kin?
Are you all right? I will take over from here,
so please head on back and get some rest.
Get out of here. That...
...is a monster among monsters.
What are you going to do?
Don't worry about me. Once I've
bought you enough time to escape,
I'll get away in no time
using teleportation magic.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Shall we get started right away, then?
Hurry and get out of here!
It would grieve me to part
so soon after meeting,
so I will block any teleportation.
Dimensional Lock.
Maximize Magic! Shard Buckshot!
A nullification ability?
Hellfire Wall!
I did not think that level of flame
would kill them. My deepest condolences.
I intended to hold back enough
to not kill them, based on you as a standard.
Why did you team up together,
when there is such disparity in your abilities?
Don't you say that about them!
Aspect of the Devil: Giant Arm of the Demon.
Translocation Damage!
Penetrate Maximize Magic! Crystal Dagger!
Even with magic to penetrate
his defense, he's unharmed?
Aspect of the Devil: Razor Sharp Claws!
I can't get away
while taking those two with me.
Which means...
Let's do this!
So then, which one of you...
...is my foe?